Oh, hello!
I have a body part that I want to shish here and there.
Secret
I once bumped into one of your supporters at the front of the line.
Me too.
Have you?
Oh no! What are the chances of that?
If there's a strange adult, I'll just yell at him or her.
I'm kind of shy.
Same here.
Me too.
I'm really nervous. I don't know if that's a good thing.
I'm really nervous. She's too cute. I get nervous when we make eye contact.
I can't make eye contact. I'll look here and talk to her.
I wonder if this is the right place to talk to her.
Thank you for coming to our store today.
Thank you for coming in today.
What do you keep in mind when it comes to style?
I see. I saw Kismin's photogravure.
I saw it, too. One word to describe it.
Nice body. Really? She's so beautiful.
You're so beautiful. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm full... of drinks. I'd like to ask you something.
I'd like to hear about it. I've got nothing to say.
I like tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen.
So I eat a lot... and then I don't know what I'll do at work the next day.
I don't know what's wrong with me. I don't know what's wrong with me at all.
I'm so concerned about myself. I've had a lot of things happen, like my face getting all puffy.
I've been looking at all your magazines, and I think you guys are so stylized.
So how do you keep your body shape?
Nice body? I was wondering how you keep your body in good shape and nice body and whatnot.
I'm trying to limit the amount of food I eat.
I reduce the amount of food I eat before important photo shoots.
Also, I have some parts of my body that I want to embroider.
For example, I want to keep the waist.
For example, I would like to keep the flesh of my waist when embroidering.
If I think I like it, I want to keep that flesh, but I want to tighten my abdominal muscles, so I watch youtube and do sit-ups and so on.
I'm trying to reduce the amount of weight by doing things like watching youtube and doing sit-ups and putting on weight where it needs to be put on.
I go to kickboxing.
Kickboxing? Kickboxing? I've seen a little bit of it.
It's an exercise, but it's good for your strength, and it's good for your abs.
What are you thinking when you kick? It's a secret.
Secret? Well, you know, it's just... it's just... if there's a crazy adult around...
I'd be like, "Oh, my God, I'm going to go kickboxing.
Whenever I have a bad day, I just punch the target.
It's a good target. It's true that it stresses you out.
So when I go after a stressful day, my teacher compliments me on my punching power.
You're a strong puncher. That's a very good thing to hear.
Kickboxing is very beneficial. I do it, remembering bad things.
I'll do it while remembering the things I don't like.
Orders.
What do you do when you meet a fan at the front?
I've bumped into supporters at the front of the line.
Me too. Have you? Oh my God, what are the odds of that?
I thought it was my problem.
It's like this, isn't it?
In my case, I went to the front of the line, took off my clothes, and rattled around.
And when I came in, they all turned this way, and one of the faces I saw was a familiar face.
I closed the door once, but I felt like I didn't make a good impression on them, so I kind of ignored them.
And I'm pretty sure they're looking at me naked too, and I'm pretty sure they know, so I'm like, what am I going to do?
I said, "Tell me what to do. That's amazing.
Later that day, she came to the benefit and we talked, and she said the same thing, "Nice party.
She said it was a really nice party, but I was so embarrassed.
But she's pretty good at it too.
She's usually shy about things like that, especially since she called me a nice party today.
Nanako, you know, I'm already traumatized.
What was the scene? We were in the sauna.
And then I thought, "Okay, I'll go get cleaned up.
And you were sitting on a bench.
On the bench? Just like that.
And he was like, "Excuse me, sir, I'm always rooting for you.
Oh, so that's how you feel? Like that?
Like, "Can we do it here?
That's true.
It's more like, "You're doing it.
That's what I'd do.
What would Yuichi do?
What if we meet?
If I meet him...
I'll be cheerful.
I don't think it'll matter if I text or not.I don't think it's a good idea to write anything once I've met you.
We've met.
Say hello.
And you're holding a microphone.
You're right.
He said, "I'll never forget my idol.
He said he'd go away and we'd get to know each other a little better.
"See you later.
The result is that you're holding a microphone.
"I'm pretty good at being an idol.
The idol I'm secretly pushing for
I love Airi Suzuki.
I've made it known that I love her.
I've said so publicly.
And as for secretly liking her...
I haven't talked to her much.
I've never heard of her.
Well, there's someone else.
What is it?
From Angelem.
Wakana Matsumoto.
She was born in 2007.
I was born in 2000.
I'm seven years younger than you.
Since the audition
She's been shining so bright since her audition.
Her singing and expressive power is amazing.
That's why she's such a good singer.
I don't know why she has so much guts.
I don't know.
When I think about what I was doing when I was 15
She looks like she's snotty.
He's snotty because he's climbing a tree.
That's right.
I thought it was cool.
I'm a little embarrassed to say this, but...
You guys...
I've been following you guys on social media.
That's right.
I've been following you guys.
What?
Nanako's sister runs the account.
Mitaka-san.
She's so cute!
I like looking at that.
Is that...
You're being filmed.
I don't even notice.
That's right.
It's been passed around all by itself.
It's so cute how off you look.
You're right.
I like it.
Maybe it's their reputation.
I heard it's really good.
Really.
Nanako...
"Nanako really likes Mikana Yamamoto from NMB48.
Mikana Yamamoto from NMB48.
What type?
Cute or beautiful?
The kind of girl that every girl dreams of.
She really is a national treasure with a beautiful face.
Heh~
I wonder what she looks like.
I know.
I know what it's like.
There's a song called "Walky.
The song is called "Walky.
Mikana is really great.
She's so cute.
Look at her.
She's so cute!
She's the best!
And there's a part where she sits down in the chorus.
So cute!
She looks like a doll.
The way the bangs are parted and swept is perfect.
Perfect.
It's perfect.It's perfect.
I had the opportunity to walk Kansai Connection once.
At that time, the person in front of me was Mikana Yamamoto.
And I secretly thought that the idol I had been secretly pushing for was right in front of me.
I took her picture, but she was so kind.
Wow, how nice!
Can I ask you one more question?
I have one more.
What do you do when you lose confidence?
Wow, I have one.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't like this.
I don't like it... you know, anti-comments...
Yes, a little bit.
I lose confidence because of it.
When do I lose confidence?
I don't have it all the time.
You don't look like you do.
It's always been pretty low.
But my fans often praise me in the comments.
I'm encouraged by them, but...
I sleep on it and forget about it.
That's true, but it's the best.
Sleep is good.
But there are times when you just can't fall asleep.
When you close your eyes...
I think about it, don't I?
I don't know what to do in those situations.
I see.
But I've been thinking about taking a sauna.
But a really hot sauna.
And if I can't have a sauna...
I'll make the bath at home really hot.
Won't that burn you?
It gets really red, too.
You're a spartan, aren't you?
That's great.
But I highly recommend it.
What temperature do you recommend?
Like 45, 6 degrees.
It's pretty lukewarm.
What temperature do you use?
Me?
What?
Is your water heater broken?
Is it broken?
50 degrees?
It's probably on.
What? Oh, shit.
50 degrees. It's probably melted.
Oh, my God. - Are you sure?
Oh, my God.
No, it feels great.
It feels good.
What's wrong with you?
Don't be such an asshole.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What did you say?
I've never heard that before.
I'm telling you the truth.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm sorry... about taking a hot bath and forgetting all about the bad stuff.
I usually do.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the water company.
I'm sorry, I have to go to the plumbing company.
It's broken.
Well, you should go.
But I can't remember.
I can't remember.
Pinky's still up.
He's cute.
Oh, my God.
So cute!
I can feel the distance.
Please subscribe to our channel!